Guide to the Elmer J. Holland Papers, 1937-1968 AIS.1968.23
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Special Files, IV.
  - Subject File, 3.
    - H.R. 3727 Eldercare (Box 242, Folder 10)
    - Employment Compensation, Bureau of (Box 242, Folder 11)
    - H.R. 2450 Engineering Bill 85th Congress (Box 243, Folder 1)
    - Engineering Bill and Data (Box 243, Folder 2)
    - Engineering Bill (Box 243, Folder 3)
    - Hearings H.R. 2450, May 13 16, 1958 (Box 243, Folder 4)
    - Engineering Bill Rough Draft Background Material (Box 243, Folder 5)
    - H.R. 2450. Summarized Information (Box 243, Folder 6)
    - Engineering Speech and material (Box 243, Folder 7)
    - Working papers (Box 243, Folder 8)
    - Engineering Bill Questionnaires. (Box 244, Folder 1)
    - Questionnaires returned. (Box 244, Folder 2)
    - Returns from institutions arranged by states. (Box 244, Folder 3)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission. Information and general. (Box 245, Folder 1)
    - Erie Ohio Canal (Box 245, Folder 2)
    - Excise Tax (Box 245, Folder 3)
    - Excise Tax Information (Box 245, Folder 4)
    - EXPO, 1967 (Box 245, Folder 5)
    - F General (Box 245, Folder 6-7)
    - Farm Scandal and otherwise (Box 245, Folder 8)
    - Farmers Bulletins (Box 245, Folder 9)
    - Farmers Union (Box 245, Folder 10)
    - Farm Income (Box 245, Folder 11)
    - Federal Aid. County. (Box 246, Folder 1-3)
    - Federal Aid. 20th District. Total (Box 247, Folder 1)
    - Federal Aid: Braddock (Box 247, Folder 2)
    - Federal Aid: Braddock Hills (Box 247, Folder 3)
    - Federal Aid: Chalfant (Box 247, Folder 4)
    - Federal Aid: Clairton (Box 247, Folder 5)
    - Federal Aid: Dravosburg (Box 247, Folder 6)
    - Federal Aid: Duquesne (Box 247, Folder 7)
    - Federal Aid: East McKeesport (Box 247, Folder 8)
    - Federal Aid: East Pittsburgh (Box 247, Folder 9)
    - Federal Aid: Elizabeth (Box 247, Folder 10)
    - Federal Aid: White Oak (Box 247, Folder 11)
    - Federal Aid: Swissvale (Box 247, Folder 12)
    - Federal Aid: Port Vue (Box 247, Folder 13)
    - Federal Aid: Mount Oliver (Box 247, Folder 14)
    - Federal Aid: Munhall (Box 247, Folder 15)
    - Federal Aid: North Braddock (Box 247, Folder 16)
    - Federal Aid: Liberty (Box 247, Folder 17)
    - Federal Aid: Lincoln (Box 247, Folder 17)
    - Federal Aid: Forward Township (Box 247, Folder 18)
    - Federal Aid: North Versailles (Box 247, Folder 19)
    - Federal Aid: Rankin (Box 247, Folder 20)
    - Federal Aid: Turtle Creek (Box 247, Folder 21)
    - Federal Aid: Trafford (Box 247, Folder 22)
    - Federal Aid: Wilmerding (Box 247, Folder 23)
    - Federal Aid: Versailles (Box 247, Folder 24)
    - Federal Aid: West Homestead (Box 247, Folder 25)
    - Federal Aid: West Mifflin (Box 247, Folder 26)
    - Federal Aid: Glassport (Box 247, Folder 27)
    - Federal Aid: Homestead (Box 247, Folder 28)
    - Federal Aid: McKeesport (Box 247, Folder 29)
    - Federal Aid to Education, 1961 (Box 247, Folder 30)
    - Federal Aid to Education Bill letters (Box 247, Folder 31)
    - Federal Aid Pittsburgh (Box 248, Folder 1)
    - Federal Aid State (Box 249, Folder 1)
    - Federal Aviation Agency (Box 249, Folder 2)
    - Federal Aviation Agency. "Federal Aid Airport Program." Fiscal year, 1960 (Box 249, Folder 3)
    - F.C.C. Federal Communications Commission (Box 250, Folder 1-3)
    - FCC Elizabeth Boro, October 1962-July 1963 (Box 250, Folder 4)
    - FCC Elizabeth Boro, August 1963 (Box 250, Folder 5)
    - Federal Contracts (Box 250, Folder 6)
    - Federal Food Stamp (Box 250, Folder 7)
    - Federal Housing Administration FHA (Box 250, Folder 8)
    - Federal Register (Box 250, Folder 9)
    - Federal Scholarships (Box 250, Folder 10)
    - Federal Surplus State Headquarters (Box 250, Folder 11)
    - Federal Trade Commission (Box 251, Folder 1)
    - Fish and Wildlife Service (Box 251, Folder 2)
    - Flag Requests closed (Box 251, Folder 3)
    - Flag Requests, 1965 (Box 251, Folder 4)
    - Flags 89th Congress, 1965-1966 (Box 251, Folder 5)
    - Flag Requests, 1966 (Box 251, Folder 6)
    - Flags 90th Congress (Box 251, Folder 7)
    - Flags Memos to architect (Box 251, Folder 8)
    - Flood Control. Prior to E.J.H. (Box 252, Folder 1)
    - Turtle Creek Flood Project (Box 252, Folder 2)
    - Turtle Creek Flood Control. Report. (Box 252, Folder 3)
    - Turtle Creek Flood Control. School Board Resolutions (Box 252, Folder 4)
    - Turtle Creek Flood Control. Press Release Radio (Box 252, Folder 5)
    - Turtle Creek Flood Control. Newspaper clippings. (Box 252, Folder 6)
    - Flood Control. Munhall. (Box 252, Folder 7)
    - Flood Control. Trafford Borough (Box 252, Folder 8)
    - Flood Control. Wall Borough and Pitcairn. (Box 252, Folder 9)
    - Flood Control. Yough Valley (Box 252, Folder 10)
    - Flood Control. Miscellaneous (Box 252, Folder 11)
    - Kinzua Dam (Box 252, Folder 12)
    - Flood Control Rowlesburg, Stonewall Jackson and Youghiogheny River Reservoirs (Box 253, Folder 1)
    - Flouridation in Water (Box 253, Folder 2)
    - Flouridation (Box 253, Folder 3)
    - Food -world crisis. (Box 253, Folder 4)
    - Foreign Affairs (Box 253, Folder 5-6)
    - Foreign Affairs, aid, relations, etc. See A.I.D. (Box 253, Folder 7)
    - Foreign Aid, 1962 (Box 253, Folder 8)
    - Foreign Aid (Box 253, Folder 9)
    - Foreign Claims Settlement Commission (Box 254, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Competition. Wages, imports, etc. (Box 254, Folder 2)
    - Foreign Government International Politics (Box 254, Folder 3)
    - Foreign Policy, 1962-1963 (Box 254, Folder 4)
    - Foreign Policy, 1963 (Box 254, Folder 5)
    - Foreign Trade, 1962-1963 (Box 254, Folder 6)
    - Foreign Trade, 1962 (Box 254, Folder 7)
    - Ford Foundation, 1962-1963 (Box 254, Folder 8)
    - Form Letters, 1957-1962 (Box 255, Folder 1)
    - Form Letters, Copies of beginning 88th (Box 255, Folder 2)
    - Fulton, James. Eddie Jensen Democratic Headquarters. (Box 255, Folder 3)
    - G -general (Box 255, Folder 4-5)
    - General Electric Plant (Box 255, Folder 6)
    - General Services Administration (Box 255, Folder 7)
    - Glass Company Glassport, Pa. (Box 256, Folder 1)
    - Glenwood Highway Bridge (Box 256, Folder 2)
    - Gold (Box 256, Folder 3-4)
    - Government Printing Office (Box 256, Folder 5)
    - Governor's Commission of Higher Education, February 1957 (Box 256, Folder 6)
    - G.O.P. -Propaganda, 1962 (Box 256, Folder 7)
    - Gun Legislation, 1967-1968 (Box 256, Folder 8)
    - H -general (Box 257, Folder 1-2)
    - Hazelwood Project. MDTA. (Box 257, Folder 3)
    - Hazelwood Glenwood Urban Extension Council (Box 257, Folder 4)
    - Head Start (Box 257, Folder 5)
    - Health, Community (Box 257, Folder 6)
    - Health, Department (Box 257, Folder 7)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare Department (Box 257, Folder 8)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare Department Office of Education (Box 257, Folder 9)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare Department Pictures and biographies (Box 257, Folder 10)
    - High Speed Transportation (Box 258, Folder 1)
    - Highway Beautification (Box 258, Folder 2)
    - Higher Education Act, 1967 (Box 258, Folder 3)
    - Highways and Sewers (Box 258, Folder 4)
    - Highways and Sewers closed. (Box 258, Folder 5)
    - Highway Department Requests closed (Box 258, Folder 6)
    - Housing -elderly (Box 258, Folder 12)
    - Highway Program (Box 258, Folder 7)
    - Homestead Valve Manufacturing Company. F.E. Schuchman, President. (Box 258, Folder 8)
    - Hospitals (Box 259, Folder 1)
    - Hospital Cases closed (Box 259, Folder 2-3)
    - Hospital Cases John J. Kane, Mayview Woodville (Box 259, Folder 4)
    - Hospital Study Commission (Box 259, Folder 5-6)
    - Hotel and Apartment Accommodations Washington (Box 260, Folder 1)
    - House/American Committee (Box 260, Folder 2)
    - Housing (Box 260, Folder 3-5)
    - Housing and Hard Money (Box 260, Folder 6)
    - Housing and Home Finance. Information and pamphlets. (Box 260, Folder 7)
    - Housing and Urban Development. General. (Box 260, Folder 8)
    - Housing and Urban Development. (Box 260, Folder 9)
    - Housing and Urban Development. Pictures and biographies (Box 260, Folder 10)
    - Department of Housing (Box 260, Folder 11)
    - Housing -elderly, 1963 (Box 260, Folder 13)
    - G.I. Housing (Box 261, Folder 1)
    - Housing Urban Affairs (Box 261, Folder 2)
    - Housing closed (Box 261, Folder 3)
    - I-General (Box 261, Folder 4)
    - Immigration Act (Box 261, Folder 5)
    - Inaugural Addresses Thank you and requests (Box 261, Folder 6)
    - Inauguration. Invitations, etc. (Box 261, Folder 7)
    - Inauguration, 1961 (Box 261, Folder 8)
    - Inauguration, 1965 (Box 261, Folder 9)
    - Income Tax complaints, refunds, etc. (Box 261, Folder 10)
    - Industrial College of the Armed forces. Conference and material (Box 261, Folder 11)
    - Industrial ralding -states, 1962 (Box 261, Folder 12)
    - IUD Industrial Union Department, 1962 (Box 261, Folder 13)
    - IDU Reports and releases, 1963 (Box 261, Folder 14)
    - Department of Interior (Box 262, Folder 1-2)
    - Interior. Picture and biographies (Box 262, Folder 3)
    - Internal Revenue Service Re: Commissioner Cohen's reply to the Readers' Digest Article (Box 262, Folder 4)
    - Internal Revenue (Box 262, Folder 5)
    - International Affairs (Box 262, Folder 6)
    - International Assoc. of Machinists (Box 262, Folder 7)
    - Iron Workers Union (Box 263, Folder 1)
    - Italo American Independent Citizen Club (Box 263, Folder 2)
    - Italian American Citizens. Not introduced resolutions (Box 263, Folder 3)
    - J -general (Box 263, Folder 4)
    - Job Corps (Box 263, Folder 5)
    - Johnson, President Lyndon B. Pictures, correspondence, etc. (Box 263, Folder 6)
    - Jury Duty (Box 263, Folder 7)
    - Justice Department. Attorney General (Box 263, Folder 8)
    - Juvenile Court (Box 263, Folder 9)
    - Juvenile Court cases closed. (Box 263, Folder 10)
    - K -general (Box 263, Folder 11-12)
    - Kane, Jone J.- Hospital (Box 263, Folder 13)
    - KDKA Editorials (Box 263, Folder 14)
    - Kennedy, President John F. Pictures, cards, etc. (Box 263, Folder 15)
    - Kiplinger Letters (Box 263, Folder 16)
    - Korean Bonus Pennsylvania (Box 263, Folder 17)
    - L -general (Box 264, Folder 1)
    - Labor -general, 1959 (Box 264, Folder 2)
    - Labor (Box 264, Folder 3)
    - Labor and Anti labor, 1968 (Box 264, Folder 4)
    - Anti-Labor (Box 265, Folder 1-3)
    - Anti Labor Publications (Box 265, Folder 4)
    - Labor Citus Picketing, minimum wage, etc. (Box 265, Folder 5)
    - Labor Committee, 1963 (Box 265, Folder 6)
    - Congressmen Endorsed by labor (Box 265, Folder 7)
    - Contracts Steel in government (Box 265, Folder 8)
    - Labor correspondence, general (Box 265, Folder 9)
    - McDonald, David J. (Box 266, Folder 1)
    - Labor Management Reporting and Disclosure Act of 1959 (Box 266, Folder 2)
    - Labor Management Relations Zelenico (Box 266, Folder 3)
    - Machinist (Box 266, Folder 4)
    - Labor material for speeches (Box 266, Folder 5)
    - Meany, George. President, AFL CIO. (Box 266, Folder 6)
    - National Labor Relations Board Bunciter, Inc. (Box 266, Folder 7)
    - National Manufacturer Association (Box 266, Folder 8)
    - National Maritime Union of America (Box 266, Folder 9)
    - Surplus Areas Defense Procurement in Labor Surplus Areas (Box 267, Folder 1)
    - Taft Hartley Act (Box 267, Folder 2)
    - Teamsters (Box 267, Folder 3)
    - Textile Workers Union of America (Box 267, Folder 4)
    - United Electrical Workers (Box 267, Folder 5)
    - United Mine Workers (Box 267, Folder 6)
    - United Rubber Workers of America CIO. Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers (Box 267, Folder 7)
    - United Steelworkers, Legislative Representatives (Box 267, Folder 8)
    - Labor Views (Box 267, Folder 9)
    - Secretary of Labor Willard Wirtz (Box 267, Folder 10)
    - Labor. Pictures and biographies (Box 267, Folder 11)
    - Workmen's Compensation Laws (Box 267, Folder 12)
    - Material on Labor (Box 268, Folder 1)
    - Labor, Department of (Box 269, Folder 1-2)
    - Labor Laws (Box 269, Folder 3)
    - Labor Laws, 1963 (Box 269, Folder 4)
    - Labor Laws, 1962 (Box 269, Folder 5)
    - Minimum Wage Unemployment Benefits Repeal Right to Work. (Box 269, Folder 6)
    - Fair Labor Standards Act (Box 269, Folder 7)
    - Landrum Griffin Bill (Box 269, Folder 8)
    - Right to Work (Box 269, Folder 9)
    - Labor (Pro and Con) (Box 271, Folder 1)
    - Labor Problems, 1962 (Box 271, Folder 2)
    - Labor Reports (Box 271, Folder 3)
    - Industrial Union Department AFL CIO (Box 271, Folder 4)
    - International Ladies Garment Workers (Box 271, Folder 5)
    - Political Action Committee (Box 271, Folder 6)
    - IUE CIO (James B. Carey) (Box 271, Folder 7)
    - Pennsylvania AFL CIO (Box 271, Folder 8)
    - Hilbert, Paul Director District 15, United Steelworker's (Box 271, Folder 9)
    - Keyserling, Leon (Box 271, Folder 10)
    - Reuther, Walter P., President United Auto Workers (Box 271, Folder 11)
    - Over 40 Employment (Box 271, Folder 1)
    - Pensioners (Box 271, Folder 2)
    - Pensioners Wesley Cotter (Box 271, Folder 3)
    - Pension Agreement (Box 271, Folder 4)
    - Railroads (Box 271, Folder 5)
    - Directory of National and International Labor Unions in the U.S. (Box 271, Folder 6)
    - Questionnaire Steelworker Employment, 1958 (Box 271, Folder 7)
    - United Steelworkers Directory local union officials, Districts 15, 16. (Box 271, Folder 8)
    - Lake Erie Ohio River Canal (Box 271, Folder 9)
    - Legislation -general (Box 272, Folder 1)
    - Legislation pending (Box 272, Folder 2)
    - Legislation pending, 1963 (Box 272, Folder 3)
    - Legislation pending, 1964 (Box 272, Folder 4)
    - Legislation pending, 1965 (Box 272, Folder 5)
    - Legislation pending, 1966 (Box 272, Folder 6)
    - Legislation pending, 1967 (Box 272, Folder 7)
    - Legislation pending, 1960 (Box 272, Folder 8)
    - Legislation results 87th Congress, 1963 (Box 272, Folder 9)
    - Legislative Reorganization Act, 1967 (Box 272, Folder 10)
    - Liaison Officers government (Box 272, Folder 11)
    - "Liberal Papers" Dem. (Box 272, Folder 12)
    - Library of Congress (Box 272, Folder 13)
    - Library of Congress. Multi-lithed reports from LRS. Legislative Reference Service (Box 272, Folder 14)
    - Libraries, 20th Congressional District (Box 273, Folder 1)
    - License -Drivers (Box 273, Folder 2)
    - Liquor Control Board (Box 273, Folder 3)
    - Liquor Control Board, 1963 (Box 273, Folder 4)
    - Literature requests, 1961 (Box 273, Folder 5)
    - Literature requests, 1964 (Box 273, Folder 6)
    - Literature requests, 1965 (Box 273, Folder 7)
    - Literature requests, 1966 (Box 273, Folder 8)
    - Literature requests, 1967 (Box 273, Folder 9)
    - Literature requests- Closed, 1960 (Box 274, Folder 1)
    - Literature requests (Box 274, Folder 2)
    - Lithuanian (Box 274, Folder 3)
    - Little League (Box 274, Folder 4)
    - Mc - general (Box 274, Folder 5-6)
    - McClelland Hearings (Box 274, Folder 7)
    - M- general (Box 274, Folder 8)
    - Magna Charta Square Deal for Workers from Cincinnati, Ohio (Box 274, Folder 9)
    - Mailing list Monthly report, 1959 (Box 274, Folder 10)
    - Manpower training Youth Training (Box 274, Folder 11)
    - Mass Transportation (Box 274, Folder 12)
    - Mass Transit (Box 274, Folder 13)
    - Mass Transit Facilities (Box 274, Folder 14)
    - Material included in diplomas of graduates (Box 274, Folder 15)
    - Margiotti, Charles J. (Box 274, Folder 16)
    - Mayview State Hospital (Box 275, Folder 1)
    - Meany, George E. (Box 275, Folder 2)
    - Medical Aid Social Security, 1963 (Box 275, Folder 3)
    - Medical Care for the Aged (Box 275, Folder 4)
    - Medical Schools (Box 275, Folder 5)
    - Medical School Letters (Box 275, Folder 6)
    - Medical Schools closed (Box 275, Folder 7)
    - Medical Care (Box 275, Folder 8)
    - Medicare (Box 275, Folder 9)
    - Medicare, 1962-1963 (Box 275, Folder 10)
    - Medical Care -aged, 1962 (Box 275, Folder 11)
    - Medical Health Insurance (Box 276, Folder 1-2)
    - AMA Reports, 1963 (Box 277, Folder 1)
    - American Medical Association. Social Security (Box 277, Folder 2)
    - AMA Social Security Medical Aid (Box 277, Folder 3)
    - Metropolitan Study Commission (Box 279, Folder 1)
    - Middle East Crisis (Box 279, Folder 2)
    - Migrant Workers closed (Box 279, Folder 3)
    - Military Government Association (Box 279, Folder 4)
    - Milk Control (Box 279, Folder 5)
    - Mine Fire Control. Bureau of Mines. (Box 279, Folder 6)
    - Minimum Wage (Box 279, Folder 7-8)
    - Miscellaneous and independent (Box 279, Folder 9)
    - Monitors, etc. H.R. 12049 (Box 279, Folder 10)
    - Morganza (Box 279, Folder 11)
    - Muske, Senator Edmund (Box 279, Folder 12)
    - N-general, 1956 (Box 280, Folder 1)
    - N -general (Box 280, Folder 2)
    - NASA. National Aeronautics and Space Administration (Box 280, Folder 3-4)
    - National Council of Senior Citizens (Box 280, Folder 5)
    - National Democratic Headquarters (Box 280, Folder 6)
    - National Foundation on the Arts and the Humanities (Box 280, Folder 7)
    - National Governor's Conference, 1967 (Box 280, Folder 8)
    - National Labor Relations Board (Box 280, Folder 9)
    - National Maritime Union (Box 280, Folder 10)
    - National Mediation Board (Box 280, Folder 11)
    - National Purpose (Box 280, Folder 12)
    - National Wildlife Federation, etc. (Box 280, Folder 13)
    - Naturalized Citizens, 1964 (Box 281, Folder 1)
    - Naturalized Citizens, beginning in January, 1964 (Box 281, Folder 2)
    - Nepotism (Box 281, Folder 3-4)
    - New Federal Building Pittsburgh (Box 281, Folder 5)
    - New House Office Building. Floor Plans. (Box 281, Folder 6)
    - Nixon, Richard (Box 281, Folder 7)
    - O-General (Box 282, Folder 1-2)
    - Obscene Literature (Box 282, Folder 3-4)
    - Obscene Literature and Pictures (Box 282, Folder 5)
    - O.E.O. Office of Economic Opportunity (Box 282, Folder 6)
    - Office Space (Box 282, Folder 7)
    - Oil (Box 282, Folder 8)
    - Oil Space (Box 282, Folder 9)
    - Oil Depletion (Box 282, Folder 10)
    - Oil vs Coal Problem (Box 282, Folder 11)
    - Older Americans (Box 282, Folder 12-13)
    - Olmsted Air Force Base. Phase out. (Box 282, Folder 14)
    - On Federal Reserve (Box 282, Folder 15)
    - Outlook immediate (Box 282, Folder 16)
    - P-General (Box 283, Folder 1-2)
    - Panama Canal Situation (Box 283, Folder 3)
    - Passports (Box 283, Folder 4-5)
    - Passports closed (Box 283, Folder 6)
    - Passports applications, 1961 (Box 283, Folder 7)
    - Passports Information and applications requests (Box 283, Folder 8)
    - Patents (Box 283, Folder 9)
    - Patent Law (Box 283, Folder 10)
    - Passes Gallery (Box 283, Folder 11)
    - Peace Corps (Box 283, Folder 12-13)
    - Penal Institutions (Box 283, Folder 14)
    - Penal Institutions closed. (Box 283, Folder 15)
    - Pennsylvania Bureau of Employment Security (Box 284, Folder 1)
    - Pennsylvania Constitutional Convention, 1967 (Box 284, Folder 2)
    - Pennsylvania Department of Public Welfare (Box 284, Folder 3)
    - Pennsylvania Department of Commerce (Box 284, Folder 4)
    - Pennsylvania Department of Highways (Box 284, Folder 5)
    - Pennsylvania Governor's Comm. of the 100,000 Pennsylvanians for the promotion of economy (Box 284, Folder 6)
    - Pennsylvania Governor's Sci. Ad. Comm. (Box 284, Folder 7)
    - Pennsylvania Governor. David L. Lawrence (Box 284, Folder 8)
    - Pennsylvania Governor. Raymond P. Shafer, 1966-1969 (Box 284, Folder 9)
    - Pennsylvania Communications Foundation (Box 284, Folder 10)
    - Pennsylvania Dairy Sanitarians Assoc. (Box 284, Folder 11)
    - Pennsylvania Democratic Study Comm. (Box 284, Folder 12)
    - Pennsylvania State Chamber of Commerce (Box 284, Folder 13)
    - Pennsylvania Facts (Box 284, Folder 14)
    - Pennsylvania Highways (Box 284, Folder 15)
    - Pennsylvania Matters (Box 285, Folder 1)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad (Box 285, Folder 2)
    - Pennsylvania Schools. Pittsburgh, etc. (Box 285, Folder 3)
    - Pennsylvania Statistics (Box 285, Folder 4)
    - Pennsylvania State Society (Box 285, Folder 5)
    - Penn State University (Box 285, Folder 6)
    - Pensions (Box 285, Folder 7)
    - Pensioners. District 16 United Steel Workers (Box 285, Folder 8)
    - P.A.C.T. closed. People Against Corrupt Taxation (Box 285, Folder 9)
    - Personnel applicants (Box 285, Folder 10)
    - Pictures correspondence, 1956-1960 (Box 286, Folder 1)
    - Pictures- correspondence (Box 286, Folder 3)
    - Pictures miscellaneous (Box 286, Folder 3)
    - Pictures Steelworker Unions correspondence (Box 286, Folder 4)
    - Pitt (Box 286, Folder 5)
    - Pitt (Appalachia, et. al) (Box 286, Folder 6)
    - Pittsburgh Activities (Box 287, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh Bicentennial Association (Box 287, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh Democratic Party (Box 287, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh Economic conditions (Box 287, Folder 4)
    - Pittsburgh Education (Box 288, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh Schools (Box 288, Folder 2-3)
    - Pittsburgh vocational education (Box 288, Folder 4)
    - Pittsburgh Federal Building (Box 288, Folder 5)
    - Pittsburgh Labor Market Study (Box 288, Folder 6)
    - Pittsburgh matters (Box 288, Folder 7-8)
    - Mayor's Committee on Human Relations (Box 289, Folder 1)
    - Model Neighborhood Program (Box 289, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh Neighborhood Services (Box 289, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh Redevelopment (Box 290, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh Regional Development Report (Box 290, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh Tax Resolutions complaints (Box 290, Folder 3)
    - Point Park Junior College general (Box 291, Folder 1)
    - Poland (Box 291, Folder 2)
    - Polio Drive (Box 291, Folder 3)
    - Polish Priests. Ignace Jan Paderewski Stamp (Box 291, Folder 4)
    - Politics funds (Box 291, Folder 5)
    - Political, 1962-1963 (Box 291, Folder 6)
    - Politics, local, 1963 (Box 291, Folder 7)
    - Politics unions (Box 291, Folder 8)
    - Polk (Box 291, Folder 9)
    - Polk Institute (Box 291, Folder 10)
    - Polk Hospital Cases closed (Box 291, Folder 11)
    - Polk Hospital and School. Hamburg, Ebensburg, etc. (Box 291, Folder 12)
    - Polk School (Box 291, Folder 13)
    - Pollution (Box 291, Folder 14)
    - Poor Peoples Campaign (Box 291, Folder 15)
    - Post Office general (Box 292, Folder 1)
    - Post Office general, 1953-1956 (Box 292, Folder 2)
    - Post Office -general. Commemorative Stamp, 1953-1961 (Box 292, Folder 3)
    - Post Office Pictures and biographies (Box 292, Folder 4)
    - Postal Bulletin. Services performed on 'Washington's Birthday' (Box 292, Folder 5)
    - Postal Union Officials (Box 292, Folder 6)
    - Postal Workers Report. Thank you letters. (Box 292, Folder 7)
    - Potatoes, 1890 (Box 293, Folder 1)
    - Poverty, 1968 (Box 293, Folder 2)
    - Poverty (Box 293, Folder 3)
    - Poverty Program. Printed material on programs offered (Box 293, Folder 4)
    - Powell, A.C. Summary Report of Investigative Task Force of the Ad Hoc Subcommittee on the War on Poverty. (Box 293, Folder 5)
    - Powell, Adam Clayton, 1967 (Box 293, Folder 6)
    - Powell. (Box 293, Folder 7)
    - Prisoners. General. (Box 293, Folder 8)
    - D.P.A. Cases closed. Department of Public Assistance (Box 293, Folder 9)
    - Public Assistance Information (Box 293, Folder 10)
    - Public Health Service (Box 293, Folder 11)
    - Public Utility Commission (Box 293, Folder 12)
    - Public Works (Box 294, Folder 1)
    - Public Works. General (APW) (Box 294, Folder 2)
    - Public Works, 1967 (Box 294, Folder 3)
    - Public Works Bill (Box 294, Folder 4)